ipaddress.is 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to Ipaddress.is. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. If for any reason you have concerns about our service or website's privacy policies, please contact us. We are committed to ensuring that every user's needs are addressed. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

When You visit Our Website, We may collect some basic Non-Personally Identifiable Information about You. We collect non-personally identifiable information about You in a number of ways, including tracking Your activities through Your IP address, computer settings, Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected in order to provide You with satisfactory service and to improve Our Website. By using this Website, You agree to the publication of Your IP address on this Website.   
We do not sell, rent or share collected information from this website. 

**Analytics**

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en)

**Advertising**

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service. These third-parties may place Cookies on Your computer, use web beacons, gather IP addresses, and log data to collect traffic and activity data in order to deliver relevant metrics, content, and advertising.  
To opt-out of interest-based advertising please visit <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>

**Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

**GDPR and Data Protection Officers**

We believe that our site is fully compliant with the GDPR. We are not in the business of processing data we are only information resource. We have made a good faith effort to update our site and make it fully compliant with GDPR. If you don't agree [contact with us](http://ipaddress.is/contact).

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

By using our site, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our privacy policy. Your use of our webiste is subject to these policies.
